<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Help Wanted</title><description>Help Wanted Issues</description><link>https://robotonomi.github.io/workspace/feed.xml</link><item>	<title>Add Carthage compatibility badge to the README</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/Archimedes/issues/38</link>	<description><![CDATA[Using  <a href="https://github.com/Carthage/Carthage/blob/7a0153cc164e301c46527f6e20c886728a0dc218/README.md#declare-your-compatibility">these instructions</a> 

.<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Improved user experience: choosealicense.com/appendix</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/703</link>	<description><![CDATA[First, I really love this page:  <a href="https://choosealicense.com/appendix">https://choosealicense.com/appendix</a> 

<br/><br/>One way it can be improved is to include some \"yes/no/undefined\" check-boxes along the top of the table.<br/>When you eg: check the box above: \"Same License\" it brings all \"same licenses\" to the top &amp; grays out all other licenses.<br/>* If you check several boxes, only those licenses with ALL checked conditions are highlighted.<br/>* Below those (partially grayed out, or something)
 are licenses that partially match the check-boxes (in decreasing number of matches)
.<br/>* And below that too is the remaining licenses, totally grayed out.<br/><br/>That would make this page awesome to use.<br/>Thanks &amp; hope this helps." ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Test that license texts match SPDX plain license texts</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/636</link>	<description><![CDATA[We should have a test that each license text in `_licenses` is the same as the plain text license in the SPDX collection to automate the requirement described at https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/blob/gh-pages/CONTRIBUTING.md#adding-a-license<br/><br/>> The text of the license should match the corresponding text found in  <a href="https://github.com/spdx/license-list-data/blob/master/text/">spdx/license-list-data</a> 

. If there are errors there, please fix them in  <a href="https://github.com/spdx/license-list-XML">spdx/license-list-XML</a> 

 (from which the plain text version is generated)
 so as to minimize license text variation and make it easier for choosealicense.com to eventually consume license texts directly from SPDX.<br/><br/>The test could clone spdx/license-list-data and compare each license we have cataloged in this project. Many existing licenses would probably have to be marked as expected failures due to bugs in SPDX output and discrepancies in how this project has cataloged some licenses. But we should address upfront for any new license cataloged here, and continue to chip away at the existing inconsistencies." ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Annotating license texts with license rules</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/441</link>	<description><![CDATA[ <a href="https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/pull/320#issuecomment-230746990">Comment/question today</a> 

 about whether EUPL-1.1 is accurately described reminded me to file this enhancement idea.<br/><br/>For each license, license rules could be annotated with ranges of text in the license pertinent to the rule. Highlighting of ranges could be turned on/off on individual license pages by selecting in the license rules (permissions/conditions/limitations)
 table. Very crude mockup taking a very simple case (the one condition of MIT)
.<br/><br/>! <a href="https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/40415/16633043/25735510-437c-11e6-84f8-1e504d48f345.png">mit-highlight-condition</a> 

<br/><br/>Obviously this is not a big help for MIT, but for longer licenses, it can be tricky to figure out what bits of the license are pertinent for a particular rule, at least if you only want to read once, which is more already than I suspect most people do.<br/><br/>Such annotations _might_ be very helpful to \"demystify\" licenses, and creating them might be good QA for choosealicense.com license descriptions.<br/><br/>Probably the simplest way to to annotate would be to have one or more full text extracts for each license for each rule, though there are other ways to do it, inline or  <a href="https://github.com/hypothesis/h/wiki/robust-anchors">out of band</a> 

.<br/><br/>Very low priority, may even be a bad idea, just recording it for now.<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Add Free Art License</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/314</link>	<description><![CDATA[ <a href="http://artlibre.org/licence/lal/en/">Free Art License 1.3</a> 

<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Internationalization / i18n / multilingual site</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/68</link>	<description><![CDATA[Would love to see about baking in I18N support to choosealicense.com proper. See #67 and #62<br/><br/>We already have the bulk of the strings in a single file (`_config.yml`)
, so it should just be a matter of abstracting out some of our variables, as far as I can tell.<br/><br/>Would love to take this on starting in August if there's interest. Would be a great exercise to set a standard for Jekyll L10N, and can iterate on some of the lessons learned form https://github.com/CMSgov/healthcare.gov.<br/><br/>@parkr any interest?<br/>@dhcole any insight / words of wisdom?<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Build `x86` on Windows with the built-in tools</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/smimesign/issues/91</link>	<description><![CDATA[We build `amd64` directly: https://github.com/github/smimesign/blob/e650daf6eaadf85c763fa06dcfb0e4d794d293dc/.github/workflows/build-binaries.yml#L89<br/><br/>But I had trouble figuring out how to build for `GOARCH=386` without errors. Right now, we use https://github.com/egor-tensin/setup-mingw to switch to 32-bit builds, which pulls down a bunch of tooling and takes a few minutes:<br/><br/>https://github.com/github/smimesign/blob/e650daf6eaadf85c763fa06dcfb0e4d794d293dc/.github/workflows/build-binaries.yml#L90-L94<br/><br/>I can't help but feel there must still be a nice (or at least much faster)
 way to do this using the built-in tools from Actions." ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Don't connect to kext when invoked with CLI args</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/SoftU2F/issues/39</link>	<description><![CDATA[We try to connect to the kext when the app starts ( <a href="https://github.com/github/SoftU2F/blob/45825a5bd6e6bad7ae9bd681c8584cbcb6e7fb7b/SoftU2FTool/U2FHID.swift#L24">code</a> 

)
. This also happens when the app is launched from the command line (Eg. for deleting/listing registrations)
. If the app is already running in the background we'll get an error because the kext only allows one connection. This error is surfaced to the user, which is confusing. We should not connect to the kext unless we need to." ]]></description></item></channel></rss>
