<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Help Wanted</title><description>Help Wanted Issues</description><link>https://robotonomi.github.io/workspace/feed.xml</link><item>	<title>Add Carthage compatibility badge to the README</title>	<link>https://github.com/github/Archimedes/issues/38</link>	<description><![CDATA[Using  <a href="https://github.com/Carthage/Carthage/blob/7a0153cc164e301c46527f6e20c886728a0dc218/README.md#declare-your-compatibility">these instructions</a> 

.<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>depends option test regression</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/613</link>	<description><![CDATA[There's a branch with the --depends option, that lists the needed (or installed)
 dependencies.<br/>This introduced a regression in the tests, so it will not be merged until it's fixed.<br/>If someone wants to have a go at finding the issue the branch is https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/tree/list_depends<br/>Closes #610 " ]]></description></item><item>	<title>No CLI parameter to specify installation path directly from command line (unable to use ubuntu-make in chef)
</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/403</link>	<description><![CDATA[Does anyone have a reliable workaround to automatically accept the default installation path when prompted? Specifically for ide eclipse-jee.<br/><br/>I tried using \"yes\", but then it doesn't set the default installation path at all and installs it into the void. \"Expect\" also gets confused, what I need is to set the installation path directly:<br/><br/>umake ide eclipse-jee --path \"/home/vagrant/.local/share/umake/ide/eclipse-jee\"<br/><br/>This would make umake useful in automatic configuration management tools (e.g. chef)
.<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Add Racket support</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/200</link>	<description><![CDATA[It would be nice if support for Racket and DrRacket would be added. Please consider it, thx :smile: <br/>http://racket-lang.org/<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Umake should safely remove all the packages it installed</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/192</link>	<description><![CDATA[When I use the \"-- remove\" argument it does not remove all the packages that were installed. It would be good if \"umake -r\" also removes the redundant packages that it installed.<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Add: Lazarus IDE and FPC</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/149</link>	<description><![CDATA[Please, add this great RAD solution. It can compile to different targets and architectures.<br/>The version provided in the USC it is old and conflicts with new versions.<br/>http://www.lazarus-ide.org/<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Support for Mono and Mono Develop</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/94</link>	<description><![CDATA[It would be nice if support for Mono and Mono Develop would be added. Please consider it :)
<br/>" ]]></description></item><item>	<title>Add Perl support</title>	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/ubuntu-make/issues/85</link>	<description><![CDATA[Please also add Perl support via perlbrew/plenv and Padre as IDE.<br/>" ]]></description></item></channel></rss>
